[Music]
hey and welcome I'm hammy and this is a
OverWatch Halloween Terror voice L and
interaction special now overwatch's
Halloween Terror events just out as well
as bringing awesome skins it's also
bought junkenstein's Revenge a fun hord
M brought with a whole bunch of new hero
voice lines and interactions possibly
following on from the events of the
junkenstein comic Link in description if
you haven't read it yet you're defending
the Lord's castle as part of a party of
four from junkenstein his and his evil
allies let me hand you over to Reinhardt
to introduce things nicely our tale is
about to begin listen to my tale I swear
that it's true of a Mad Doctor his
monster and his thirst for
Revenge Dr junkenstein had been slighted
by the Lord of Adas Brun humiliated he
vowed to destroy the castle and kill all
who had mocked him Dr junkenstein
laughed as his minions arose for tonight
was the night of junkenstein's
renge so our four Heroes defending the
castle are The Alchemist the soldier the
Gunslinger and the Archer all of whom
have their own intro lines like these
ones the tale begins in Adas Brun where
the lord of the castle has called for
Heroes to come to his Aid and defend him
against the Mad Dr
junkenstein wandering Gunslinger seeking
Adventure all seem strangely familiar as
the battle rages all the characters then
have a bunch of interactions with each
other there's loads bliz have really put
a load of effort into these so many in
fact I've gone through 8,000 files and I
know I've missed or confused a few so if
you spot any missing or slightly mixed
up do let me know in the comments below
first up here's some for Anna The
Alchemist of our tale we must stop these
Abominations created in the name of
Science Why fight for this Lord you have
never cared much for the nobility it is
true but today we share a common foe the
reaper I once met a man who could summon
a dragon as you do impossible only my
clan possesses the skill my brother
could but he is dead what reason brings
you to travel so far from home I was
banished from my home for taking my
brother's life I can never
return do you think that was the last of
them
something tells me the worst is yet to
come you do not trust my Alchemy do you
all due respect Witchcraft and magic
potions are no match for a good six
shooter next up hanso The Archers
interactions my people would call you a
ronin a masterless samurai
Ronin I like the sound of that getting
tired Gunslinger not a
chance what difference is there between
the witches magic and your Alchemy
Alchemy is a science her magic is
something darker you say you do science
the good Dr junkenstein would profess
the same science is a tool and a method
the hand that wields it decides its
course I sense that you and the soldier
have history together this is not our
first battle together and not the last
unless he does something foolish do you
think the doors will hold the doors are
not what I'm concerned about what sort
of monster do you think the reaper is
the worst kind there is a wicked man
next it's time for the Gunslinger
unsurprisingly that's McCree didn't
expect to find another American so far
from home you fighting the war I don't
stay in one place for too long came from
a town called
Bloomington Indiana
you seem awful
familiar you sure we haven't met before
maybe in another
life you don't seem like someone who'd
put his faith in alchemy you have to
believe in something may as well be the
thing that keeps you
alive what's home lag for you Archer a
village higher top a hill there are
cherry blossoms in the spring I miss it
dearly you're not bad with a bow but
don't you think it's a little
oldfashioned perhaps there is still a
future for
anachronisms hey Archer would say you
pass that flask around so we can all
have a drink this is thirsty work we
drink when the job is
done doesn't seem to be any end to the
monsters let them come I could always
use the
practice I can tell you and the soldier
have some history together indeed and
much of it
unhappy not sure how I feel about all
this Alchemy nonsense seems like Hocus
Pocus to me I could leave you to die if
you
prefer you think this Lord's good for
the money Castle looks like it's seen
better days finally the soldier no
prizes for guessing he that is what
drives a man to such
Madness you ask me you pump something
full of these chemicals electricity and
whatnot that's not a man it's a
monster the reaper is a fearsome foe he
may still get the better of us I will
get us home safe as I always do the
soldier an alchemist an Archer and an
odity a mly group we have assembled
here just as it has always been you
attract strange companions
it's time to finish this fight old
friend let us hope we have the strength
to see it
through if we survive the night this
should be our last battle no I cannot
rest until we have
Justice surely Dr junkenstein must be
running out of his machines now as the
battle progresses the reaper
junkenstein's monster junkenstein
himself then the Witch and all three
previous allies battle you there are
some real fun interactions talking about
the general progress of whichever
character you're playing as mighty blows
were struck and the doctor's Creations
fell like leaves in the
forest the soldier was unrelenting and
his enemies fell before him the
alchemist's aim was uniring her attacks
exacting a heavy toll on the doctor's
Creations the Gunslinger was Unstoppable
with each pull of the trigger another
enemy fell one after
another the Archer's aim was Peerless
his hand a blur as his arrows flew
filling the night sky with their
whispered song there are also some
customized like this to which hero kills
witch monster too or lands the killing
blow the gunslinger's shot found its
Mark and the reaper was destroyed and
some funny reactions when certain Heroes
kill certain
monsters bump now when you win there's
also a customized line depending on
which of the monsters is the last of
fall the reaper fell the enchanted
pumpkin where his head ought to have
been smashed against the
flagstones the night was quiet and the
castle was safe and as the witch fell
her magic had no more power Dr
junkenstein's Creations fell lifeless to
the Earth and as morning dawned the
castle was safe
with one last laugh Dr junkenstein fell
from the balcony to the flagstones below
and as the last of his laughter echoed
from the walls of the castle the battle
was over and the castle had been saved
and the monster fell just as his creator
exhausted battered bruised the four
Heroes entered the castle to receive
their reward
and of course there's this if you lose
the heroes fought valiantly but they
could not stop Dr junkenstein and his
Creations the castle fell The Defenders
were slain and junkenstein had his
revenge finally there's a couple of what
I think a new Ian Val interactions as
the braw uses that map I assume these
are just referring to them as a nice
little hint I've not actually heard
these in gang yet have you they used to
believe that vites lived in these Woods
ridiculous isn't it
they had the strangest dream about this
place there was a witch and a monster
and crazy right finally outside of
Halloween as a little bonus for you guys
who have stuck through to the end here
are some extra lines that I found in the
patch I think these are new do let me
know if you heard them before firstly
Mercer's got a new what I think is a
valkyrie light I am the Chooser of the
slain she's also got Mercy as summoned
Mercy as summoned Winston reflect on his
museum mission performance oh I should
have dropped a shield for those nice
kids how so doesn't want to lose his
honor I have lost my home and my brother
but I will not lose my honor Soldier 76
thinks a scar adds a certain something
bones heal pain is temporary scars look
good and may seems to have concerns
about regulations I'm on fire isn't that
against regulations the end just for
tuning into to my Halloween brawl
interactions and voice lines special let
me know how you're enjoying the event
your favorite lines and interactions and
skin of course in the comments below if
you like the vid do check out my other
OverWatch and OverWatch hero law
interactions and voice lines of VI as
well as loads more in the playlists
cheers for tuning in I've been hammy
take it easy